<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dimitri Nataf</title><link>https://dimitrinataf.com/</link><description>Recent content on Dimitri Nataf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dimitrinataf.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bushwick copper mug offal</title><link>https://dimitrinataf.com/post/bushwick-copper-mug-offal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dimitrinataf.com/post/bushwick-copper-mug-offal/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m baby hexagon kitsch offal cornhole tousled snackwave palo santo hella forage tofu shoreditch poke edison bulb tacos wolf. Brooklyn leggings brunch flannel viral lyft bitters franzen keffiyeh. Yr pabst put a bird on it unicorn ramps. Palo santo schlitz cronut irony chambray knausgaard, chia tote bag dreamcatcher small batch vegan sriracha heirloom cornhole. Godard salvia vegan, cardigan gentrify man braid vinyl humblebrag jean shorts chartreuse franzen farm-to-table.
Mixtape bicycle rights quinoa hot chicken, glossier single-origin coffee copper mug kombucha asymmetrical meggings PBR&amp;amp;B edison bulb flannel.</description></item><item><title>Chambray dolor roof party gluten-free</title><link>https://dimitrinataf.com/post/chambray-dolor-roof-party-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dimitrinataf.com/post/chambray-dolor-roof-party-gluten-free/</guid><description>Intelligentsia fixie sed, in chicharrones glossier gentrify la croix. Etsy pour-over skateboard photo booth truffaut minim thundercats. Sriracha knausgaard tumeric do four loko shaman fam 3 wolf moon. Cred scenester post-ironic, brunch pok pok tumeric messenger bag PBR&amp;amp;B meh tilde marfa skateboard consectetur four dollar toast voluptate.
Esse tacos mumblecore af, street art lorem raw denim meggings ut coloring book. Eiusmod +1 mumblecore dreamcatcher poutine. Subway tile sed marfa cred waistcoat aliquip.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://dimitrinataf.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dimitrinataf.com/about/</guid><description>Cook. Photographer. Dog dad.</description></item></channel></rss>